Guide to the John G. Brady Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1870-1925; Series VII; 8' (18 Boxes)
  - PAPER PRINTS
    - Towns
      - Mumtrekhlagamute and Kolmakovsky (Box 27, Folder 163)
      - Native Alaskan towns, 1880-99 (Box 27, Folder 164)
      - Native Alaskan towns, 1900-06 (Box 27, Folder 165)
      - Native Alaskan towns, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 166)
      - Nome, 1909-10 (Box 27, Folder 167)
      - Nushagak, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 168)
      - Ounalaska, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 169)
      - Portland, Oregon (Box 27, Folder 170)
      - St. Paul Island (Box 27, Folder 171)
      - Sitka, 1880 (Box 27, Folder 172)
      - Sitka, 1881-86 (Box 27, Folder 173)
      - Sitka, 1887-89 (Box 27, Folder 174)
      - Sitka, 1890 (Box 28, Folder 175)
      - Sitka, 1891-96 (Box 28, Folder 176)
      - Sitka, 1897-99 (Box 28, Folder 177)
      - Sitka, 1900 (Box 28, Folder 178-79)
      - Sitka, 1901-11 (Box 28, Folder 180)
      - Sitka, 1912-20 (Box 28, Folder 181)
      - Sitka, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 182-83)
      - Tanana, 1910 (Box 28, Folder 184)
      - Valdez, 1901, 1907, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 185)
      - Wrangel, 1897, 1900, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 186)
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 187)
      - Postcards, 1906-20, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 188)
    - Transportation: miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 189)
  - PHOTOGRAPH ALBUMS
    - Alaska scenes, mostly Sitka, by Partridge, c. 1890-95 (Box 28, Folder 190)
    - Alaska scenes, by Winter and Pond, c. 1898 (Box 28, Folder 191)
  - GLASS NEGATIVES
    - Memorandum and box cover (Box 28, Folder 192)
    - Totems, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 193-94)
    - Totems, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 195-96)
  - NEGATIVES
    - List, 1972 Nov 6 (Box 29, Folder 197)
    - Agriculture, 1900-01? (Box 29, Folder 198)
    - Animals, 1886-89 (Box 29, Folder 199)
    - Black Hills, Malcolm Rutherford Thorpe, 1914 (Box 29, Folder 200-03)
    - Boats, 1903-04 (Box 29, Folder 204)
    - Brady, John G.
      - Portraits, 1906 (Box 29, Folder 205)
      - Family portraits, 1891-1904 (Box 29, Folder 206)
      - Home, 1886-1916 (Box 29, Folder 207)
    - Buildings, 1887-1916 (Box 29, Folder 208)
    - Buildings, native Alaskan, 1890, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 209)
    - Fishing, 1900 (Box 29, Folder 210)
    - Landscapes, 1890, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 211)
    - Lumber, 1910, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 212)
    - Maps, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 213)
    - Native Alaskan crafts, 1886, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 214)
    - Nebraska, 1914 (Box 29, Folder 215-18)
    - Portraits, native Alaskan, 1890-1904, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 219)
    - Portraits, white, 1885, 1904, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 220)
    - Portraits, white, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 221-24)
    - Schools, 1905-10 (Box 29, Folder 225)
    - Social activities, 1898-1900, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 226)
    - Totems, 1901-06 (Box 29, Folder 227)
    - Towns: Sitka, 1889-1912, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 228)
    - Towns: Valdez, Nome, 1906, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 229)
  - PRINTING BLOCK
    - Portrait, John G. Brady, 1913 May 19 (Box 29, Folder 230)
  - GLASS LANTERN SLIDES
    - Lists of slides for lectures, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 231)
    - Agriculture, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 232-39)
    - Animals, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 240-43)
    - Boats, native Alaskan, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 244)
    - Brady, John G.; home, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 245)
    - Brady, John G. and family; portraits (Box 30, Folder 246)
    - Buildings, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 247-53)
    - Buildings, native Alaskan, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 254)
    - Churches, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 255-58)
    - Crafts, native Alaskan, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 259)
    - Dogsleds, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 260)
    - Expeditions, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 261)
    - Fishing, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 262)
    - Graphics for lectures, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 263)
    - Graves, native Alaskan, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 264)
    - Haynes, F. J. (cover slip), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 265)
    - Hunting, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 266-68)
    - Landscapes (Box 32, Folder 269-75)
    - Landscapes (Box 33, Folder 276-82)
    - Maps, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 283-88)
    - Mining, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 289)
    - Mining, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 290-300)
    - Nebraska, Hay Springs quarry, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 301)
    - Portraits, Laplanders (Box 34, Folder 302)
    - Portraits, native Alaskans, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 303-15)
    - Portraits, native Alaskans, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 316-17)
    - Portraits, whites, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 318-27)
    - Railroads, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 328-32)
    - St. Louis World's Fair, 1904, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 333)
    - Schools, native Alaskan, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 334-35)
    - Ships, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 336-40)
    - Ships, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 341-42)
    - Social activities, native Alaskan, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 343)
    - Social activities, white, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 344)
    - Timber, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 345)
    - Totems, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 346-48)
    - Towns
      - Dawson, Klondike (Box 38, Folder 349)
      - Grand Forks--Forty Mile Trading Post (Box 38, Folder 350)
      - Juneau, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 351-52)
      - Ketchikan, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 353)
      - Metlakahtla--Petersburg, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 354)
      - Pribiloff--Skyway, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 355)
      - Seward, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 356)
      - Sitka, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 357)
      - Treadwell, Valdez, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 358)
      - Wrangell, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 359)
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 360)
      - Damaged slides, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 361)
    - Villages, native Alaskan, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 362)
- City of Sitka Records, 1867-1873; Series VIII; 0.5' (1 box)
  This series is arranged by form of material--e.g., correspondence, minutes, resolutions--and chronologically under each heading.
  - Correspondence of Mayor and City Council, 1867-1868 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence of Mayor and City Council, 1869 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence of Mayor and City Council, 1870 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence of Mayor and City Council, 1871-72 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Minutes of City Council meetings, 1867-72 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions passed by City Council, 1867-68 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Resolutions passed by City Council, 1869 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Resolutions passed by City Council, 1870 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Resolutions passed by City Council, 1871-1872 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Ordinances passed by City Council, 1867 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Ordinances passed by City Council, 1868-71 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Court records, 1868-72 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Election records, 1867 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Election records, 1868-72 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Financial records, 1868 Jan-Jun (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Financial records, 1868 Jul-Dec (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Financial records, 1869 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Financial records, 1870 Jan-Sep (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Financial records, 1870 Oct-Dec (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Financial records, 1871-73 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Appendix
  - List of Photographers. Series VII
    Albertstone, Reuben; Sitka, Alaska
    Albertstone, Reuben, and L. Moosebauer; Sitka, Alaska
    American Museum of Natural History
    Barley, H. C. and Company; New York City
    Barr (?); Shanghai, China
    Bells, C. M.; Washington, D.C.
    Blankenberg
    Cantwell
    Chamberlin
    Curtis, Asabel; Seattle, Washington
    De Groff, Edward; Sitka & Juneau, Alaska
    Deweese, Dall
    Dyea
    Eaton, Thomas; Metlakahtla, Alaska
    Elite Studio
    Gifford; Portland, Oregon
    Gilben, C. M.
    Hak
    Hamilton
    Harrison Brothers
    Hartmann and Weinland
    Haynes, F. J.; St. Paul, Minnesota
    Hegg, E. A.
    Huey; Nome, Alaska
    Hunt, Phineas S.; Reynolds, Alaska
    Ingersoll, T. W.; St. Paul, Minnesota (see index of photographers)
    Jacoby Brothers; Chatanika, Alaska
    Kaiser, H. G.; Nome, Alaska
    Kopp, J. G.
    Landerskin; Juneau, Alaska
    La Roche; Seattle, Washington
    Lawrence, Sydney
    Merrill, E. W.; Boston, Massachusetts
    Nowell, F. H.
    Partridge, E. J. and W. H. Partridge; Portland, Oregon
    Peterson, George E.
    Sabaleff, Vincent; Killisnoo, Alaska
    Scherer; New York City
    Taber, I. W.; San Francisco, California (see index of photographs)
    Thwaites
    Lieutenant Todd; United States Naval Gunboat Wheeling
    Towne, B. C.; Portland, Oregon
    Townsend; New York City
    Welden
    Winter and Pond; Juneau, Alaska
    Wolfe Foto
  - INDEX OF T. W. INGERSOLL PHOTOGRAPHS
    - "Juneau (?) City, Indian Home and Canoes #3536 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - "Sitka, blockhouse, remains of Russian fortifications" #3504 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - "Sitka--Greek Church" (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - "Sitka--Greek Church interior" #3507 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - "Sitka--Indian canoe and salmon drying racks on beach" #3508 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - "Crevasse--Muir Glacier" #3519 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - "Muir Glacier, sea face and mountains" (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - "Muir Glacier ocean frontage" #3516 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - "Muir Glacier--edges of ice, near view glacier field" #3520 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - "Indian and black faced squaw tanning bears skin" #3539 (Box 24, Folder 82)
    - [Native women] (Box 25, Folder 95)
    - "Indian River Bridge--Sitka" #3511 (Box 25, Folder 102)
    - "Muir Glacier, group of tourists on ice burg" #3523 (Box 25, Folder 102)
    - "Muir Glacier--sea front--tourists among stranded ice burgs" #3521 (Box 25, Folder 107)
    - "Ft. Wrangel, street of Indian village and totem poles" #3547 (Box 27, Folder 148)
    - "Indian street and totem poles--Ft. Wrangel" #3550 (Box 27, Folder 148)
    - "Ft. Wrangel, totem poles in front of Indian (Box 27, Folder 148)
    - "Indian burial house and totem poles, whale and wolf--Ft. Wrangel" #3552 (Box 27, Folder 148)
    - "Ft. Wrangel--totem pole" #3558 (Box 27, Folder 148)
    - "Ft. Wrangel--street in Indian town and totem poles" (Box 27, Folder 148)
    - "Ft. Wrangel from Indian village" (Box 27, Folder 164)
    - "Ft. Wrangel--street view Indian quarters" #3543 (Box 27, Folder 164)
    - "Sitkan archipelago southward from Baranov Castle and Mount Edgecomb," and "Archipelago from Baranov Castle" (Box 27, Folder 172)
  - INDEX OF I. W. TABER PHOTOGRAPHS
    - [Portraits of John G. Brady] (2) (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - "Old government buildings, Sitka, Alaska" (Box 28, Folder 175)
    - Glass lantern slides
      - "Winter house at Pt. Belcher, Alaska" (Box 31, Folder 254)
      - "Native huts, Siberia" (Box 31, Folder 254)
      - "Selawick River Indian" (Box 35, Folder 303)
      - "Women of St. Lawrence Island" (Box 35, Folder 306)
      - "Cape Navarin natives, Siberia" (Box 35, Folder 311)
      - "School girl--Pt. Barrow, Alaska" (Box 35, Folder 312)
      - "Alaskan coast natives at Icy Cape" (Box 35, Folder 314)
      - "Indian girl, Eskimo" (Box 35, Folder 315)
      - "Indian woman and child, from interior of Alaska" (Box 35, Folder 316)
      - "Revenue cutter 'Bear' in the ice--Behring Sea" (Box 35, Folder 337)
      - "Revenue cutter 'Bear' at Ounalaska" (Box 35, Folder 337)
      - "Sitka from an island to west" (Box 35, Folder 357)